whowon.com 2003-06-03

# WhoWon.com Privacy Policy

WhoWon.com is committed to providing you the opportunity for a positive experience during your visit to our web site, while respecting and striving to protect your on-line privacy. Because protecting your privacy is very important, we have adopted this policy to safeguard your personal information and protect its confidentiality. We will limit the collection and use of personal information to what is necessary to administer our business, provide you with the highest quality visit, and offer you information we think will be of interest. We will not disclose any individual information to other organizations.

To facilitate navigation, this site may contain links to other sites. We will make every effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. However, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by organizations sponsoring these other sites.

**A. Basic Statement** :

WhoWon.com collects personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis only. Personal information may include name, title, company, address, phone number, e-mail address, etc. The individual information we collect is used only to facilitate the on-line experience through enhanced navigation or to suggest areas in which we may improve the structure and content of the site. We do not sell, rent or transmit personal information to other organizations.

**B. Collection and Use** :

Our web server tracks and collects general information about your visit to our website. We collect these statistics to determine the number of daily visitors to our site, the daily requests for particular files, the types of browsers our visitors use, the visitors' domain names, and countries of origin.

This data helps us to customize our website to better meet your on-line needs, so we may request and store the following types of specific information: your name, company name, street address, city, county, state, country, province, telephone numbers and e-mail addresses. This personally identifiable information is only collected when voluntarily submitted by a visitor in one of our on-line information or e-mail correspondence forms.

This site, WhoWon.com, uses the services of BURST! Media for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. All users who receive an ad served by BURST! retain complete anonymity where BURST! is concerned. As ads are delivered, BURST! does not acquire or collect any personal information about you. Your name, address, phone number, and email address all remain your private properties. The BURST! Media privacy policy can be viewed at <http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp>.

**C. Storage and Access** :

All personal information you provide to WhoWon.com is secured on our server with restricted access. We reserve the right to use agents, who are bound by strict confidentiality guidelines, to perform storage and processing functions. Only designated employees or agents who need to carry out legitimate business functions are permitted to view your personal data. Employees or agents who violate this privacy policy are subject to disciplinary actions, up to and including termination.

**D. Disclosure** :

Because WhoWon.com considers the individual information we maintain to be confidential, our policy is to disclose no personal information to third parties unless release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or government investigations or proceedings.

WhoWon.com will occasionally carbon-copy form submissions to WhoWon.com in order to evaluate visitor demographics and police possible piracy.

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence of the new privacy policy.
